No way! Am I awake? Is this real life right now?
And, um, this is one of my favorites, too.
This is ridiculously huge!
You look like a literal angel! Like an angel!
Oh my god, Shinju! Did you take all of this?
Yeah, I did.
You're so talented! You've got such a great eye! I mean it! Like, wow!
What a nice thing to say. Thank you.
All I wanted was for her to take photos for me.
Then she decided to create an account and give me a cosplay name.
Really?
What made you do that?
Well, uh...
She just... she never wanted to show anyone her photos.
And I was so proud of how adorable she looked and wanted other people to see her like I did.
So I asked her if I could make an account to post them and she said yes.
She got so many likes and comments, it was amazing!
People were posting tons of nice things about her on all the photos.
The problem is that it got to be so overwhelming, I had no idea how I was supposed to respond.
So I just ended up ignoring all of them.
That's why no one ever got a response from her!
Mm-hmm.
I'm not cosplaying for their approval.
I do it for me, I don't care what they think.
Yeah, I know that.
But look at the amount of followers you have now.
Isn't it amazing that people love what you love?
I know how happy it makes me to see it.
That's so sweet!
What is?
How much you love your sister.
I'm glad you have each other.
Yes, I love her so much!
Oh?
And I can tell you feel the same way, Juju.
Ew, don't tell me how I feel.
I know how I feel.
This is what we use.
Our dad's DSLR.
Nice!
Is your dad a professional photographer or something?
Not at all.
He just does it for fun.
So fancy!
I love this camera because you don't have to change the lens for effects or different lighting.
That's interesting.
But when would you switch out the lens?
It really depends on what you're going for.
It's fun to experiment!
Each lens makes it look totally different even when it's the same shot.
Question?
Yes?
What is it?
Is it that much better to use a camera than it is to use a smartphone?
Yes.
The camera gives you a higher resolution and there's so much more you can do.
For example, if you take a photo with flowers in the background, you can blur those flowers a bit to make the cosplayers stand out more.
Or you can blur the foreground and give the photo a softer vibe overall.
If petals or leaves are falling, you can adjust the shutter speed to keep them from looking blurry.
Wow, that's amazing.
Yeah, for real.
It sounds so fun.
It is.
I love getting a picture to turn out exactly how I want, or capturing a unique expression out of the blue.
It inspires me.
I always want to learn more so I can take even better photos.
Plus, you're taking pics of Juju!
She's like the best model there is!
Yeah.
Just curious, why don't you ever do cosplay, Shinju?
I mean, you're pretty much around them all the time.
Don't you want to try it too?
There's no way you can watch Juju do so many adorable ones and not want to get in on the fun!
I don't know.
Tell the truth, do you want to?
No, no.
I don't want to do it.
I just love taking pictures for my sister.
I could never cosplay myself.
That's cool, I guess.
Thanks.
So, uh, can I try your camera for a sec?
Sure.
Whoa, this thing rocks!
I would love to learn how to take a shot with all the fuzzy background tricks!
I'm so saving up for one of these!
You said it's a DSLR?
How much do those typically cost?
Oh, here we go.
Huh?
Why would they sell the lens separately?
Dude, you're so loud!
You can add a flash, a tripod, and the rest of it if you want to go broke.
Huh?
You look funny when your mind's blown.
But at the cosplay event, pretty much everyone had a camera like that.
How do people afford them?
I know, it's crazy!
It might take a while to save up, so let's keep taking pics with our phones for now.
Okay.
Guess she's determined to get one regardless.
There are other cameras, you guys.
I'm sure you can find one in your budget.
Oh, by the way, we're gonna scout a location later if you want to come with us.
This is the first time I'm renting a studio, so I want to know what options are out there.
OMG!
That sounds like so much fun!
I'm in!
I would actually love to go too.
Word.
Let's meet up at Shin Misato Station this weekend.
Okay!
Just as a warning, the space is in an abandoned hospital.
Oh, wow.
I didn't know there were studios like this.
I know, right?
My first abandoned building.
Yeah, same!
Cool.
I'm so excited.
I couldn't even sleep last night because of it.
No freaking way!
It's like a horror flick in here!
Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
This is great.
Especially since there is an abandoned hospital scene.
Black Lily hides there after Princess Daisy defeats her.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, it's super depressing.
But I really like the scene where Shion starts to question her own sanity.
But what's most important is that you really did watch the whole thing.
Hey, Gojo!
We're going upstairs!
Don't get killed!
I'll try.
You ready, Shinju?
I guess this place is a little on the creepy side, isn't it?
You okay, Inui?
Yeah, of course!
You don't sound too sure about that.
Do places like this make you uncomfortable?
What?
Why would you even ask me that?
I shoot in dark locations all the time!
You're slowing us down!
Let's go!
I'll take that as a yes.
I mean...
So what if it has murder vibes, am I right?
I'm just worried it might be too dark to shoot.
Nah, we have a flash.
It's fine.
You're such a superhero.
Flashes and reflectors are the heroes.
They can be used in outdoor shoots as well.
So they're important to have.
Even if it's sunny?
Yep.
Natural light is awesome, but it's hard to keep your eyes open in the sun.
That's why we make it the backlighting.
It creates a beautiful soft light on your skin.
Though, it also casts dark shadows all over your face.
Oh, I know!
Then you use reflectors to bring your face back!
You got it!
It also makes the wigs nice and shiny, and improves your complexion, too!
That's so lit!
Like, literally.
I gotta tell Gojo!
Backlighting is the best!
It looks like it's gonna rain.
Yeah.
Man.
I'd love to do a shoot outside someday when the weather's not so blah.
Come to think of it, where do you guys usually go to take outdoor photos?
Just our backyard.
It's really coming down.
Hey, what's going on?
Inui?
It's fine!
Everything's fine!
I'm just a little tired!
That's not even a little convincing.
Would you rather wait by the entrance?
Heck no!
I'm going to cosplay Black Lily no matter what.
I just have to get comfortable with the location, or I'll have an awkward expression in every photo.
Want me to take a look around for you?
Don't worry, you can go on back.
Seriously?
I can handle this myself!
Yeah, I know.
But it seems like a lot.
Is there a reason you're pushing so hard?
My dreams.
Don't you ever plan for the future?
Yes.
I want to be a kashirashi.
It's a kind of artist that designs the faces of Hina dolls.
That's a lovely dream.
Good luck making it come true.
I couldn't.
I always wanted to become a magical girl.
I admired their strength, optimism, and confidence.
Fighting battles in cute, frilly outfits.
I've looked up to them since I was little.
I was obsessed.
I really thought I could become one when I got older.
But once you start school, you learn the truth.
It's all make-believe.
None of it's real.
I learned that no matter how hard I worked or prayed,
my dream of being a magical girl would never come true.
Then one day, when I was in middle school,
I discovered that I could at least look like them for a while.
I'd never cosplayed before, so I had no clue how to style the wig.
I didn't even put makeup on.
And the outfit wasn't tailored, so it was way too big.
To be honest, my first attempt at cosplay was a mess, but...
I didn't care.
Just wearing it made me so happy.
I found a way to make all my dreams come true.
Even if it's make-believe, the way I feel is real.
Can I ask you something?
Sure, what?
This outfit is important to you.
So why'd you ask me to make it?
There are so many people who are better at this than I am.
People with real experience.
Why don't you pick one of them instead?
Honestly, it's because of the photos Maureen posted.
I was jealous.
I know how pathetic and lame that sounds, believe me.
But it's the truth.
I couldn't stop obsessing over it.
I felt like the only way to calm my inner rage was to have an outfit made by the same person, no matter who they were.
And you're right.
There are many others who can make the same outfit.
But still...
I'm sorry.
I'm not explaining this very well.
It's not logical.
Seeing that outfit was like...
Love at first sight.
There's something about it I can't explain.
I know how this must sound to you.
Honestly, I'm surprised my feelings are so strong.
But I've heard that jealousy is something you only feel about things that truly matter.
These are called Hina dolls.
Pretty, aren't they?
I made them with some of my old pals.
Do you like them?
Mm-hmm.
A lot.
I love them.
They're so beautiful.
The most beautiful in the world, I say.
At this shop, we work hard every single day to make sure our dolls catch the eyes.
We want our customers to think they're the best ever made.
Because they are to us.
So I'm glad that you like them.
Very glad.
What's catch the eyes mean, Grandpa?
Hmm?
Uh, that's a tough one to explain.
I guess we want people to fall in love with them at first sight.
Me too.
Hmm?
I can't wait to grow up.
I'm gonna make Hina dolls just like these ones.
I want to be like you, Grandpa.
With plenty of practice, you can make these someday just like your Grandpa.
Grandpa.
Wait, what's happening?
Why are you crying, you weirdo?
Is this about the outfit?
You don't have to do it if you're gonna be dramatic about it!
Say something, get it!
What's wrong with you?
That's one of the most amazing things I've ever heard!
Because of you, I now understand how happy Grandpa was back then.
How much his art meant to him.
I never imagined it felt anything like this!
I'm so grateful to you, Inui.
I promise to never forget what you talked about!
At 17, Sajuna Inui went through an awakening of her own that day.
As a student at an all-girls school, this was the first time she'd ever held hands with a boy.
So her brain short-circuited.
Oh no!
Inui?
Are you okay?
Wake up!
Speak to me, Inui!
Can you hear me?
Hello?
Help!
Someone help!
We did it!
We're done!
Hey, Kojo!
It's beach time, dude!
Let's go!
It's not quite warm enough to swim yet.
That's why there's like no one around.
Pretty cool, huh?
It's almost like our own private beach.
What are we even doing here?
So, um, did we come here to take some photos or something?
Hmm?
Well, the other day, you said you wanted to try backlit photos, so...
Is that why we're at the beach?
Huh?
No, it's not about that, silly!
We're done with finals, aren't we?
Yeah.
And?
It's July, isn't it?
And that's summer, right?
So I wanted to go!
That's all.
Straight from the classroom to the edge of the ocean, we have the epic power of youth!
Of course our reason for bringing us here is totally random!
Let's get to go for you.
Definitely eating from this place again.
Gojo, are you gonna eat all of your fries?
No.
Give me some, give me some, give me some fries!
Uh...
Huh?
Hey!
Give me back my burger!
Huh?
Is that klepto-buzzard following us?
Maybe we should go find somewhere else to eat.
Nah, I'm not scared of some fat bird.
Let's have bubble tea by the ocean.
It'll be so adorable.
We even brought a mat.
Screw that beach pigeon.
Live on the edge, Gojo!
Okay.
That's it.
You're quitting already?
Leave us and our french fries alone!
Now's our chance.
Let's make a break for it.
We can't let him get our last burger.
Tch!
Oh!
I shouldn't have littered.
Sorry.
Come on!
Later, Mr. Hamburglar!
Here you go.
That one's yours.
Are you sure?
Very.
Well, thanks
It's super good
Thank you
You weren't kidding
This is really delicious
Right?
Yo, this bubble tea is legit
Try it, Gojo
No, I'm good, thank you, though
Your loss
I could sit in this breeze forever
Yeah, feels great
Okay
This is the moment
Here, pull this, thanks
Wait, are you gonna swim?
Ew, no
I'm just gonna soak my feet
I didn't bring a swimsuit
It was a last minute thing
I'm going in
She's such a free spirit
No way
Bro, look
I just got two wiggly seaweeds
Check it out
They're so slimy and cool
Look at them
I'm looking
Gojo, let's go, go
Don't stay on the beach
Like a crabby crab
Right, coming
Hurry up, come on
I'm trying
Just give me a minute
You're kidding, it's really cold
Wait, what's happening?
It feels like my feet are sinking
Okay, easy, just breathe
Not like it's your first time, right?
Well, yeah, it is
Huh?
No way
Really?
Well, I guess Saitama is pretty landlocked
Yeah, but it isn't exactly that
I just don't get out much
Ever since I was little
The only things I've done for fun
Are look at Hina dolls
And practice painting them
I loved it so much
I never wanted to do anything else
So now, there are a lot of things I haven't done yet
Grandpa was right
He told me I should get out and explore more
I wish I had listened
This is nothing like what I've seen on TV or in photos
Turns out, I love the beach
It's beautiful
Well, then we've got a lot of catching up to do
And summer vacation's here
So it's on
You're coming with me everywhere
I mean it
Let's go
Just
You and me
Huh?
Are you sure?
Because I would love to
I'm excited
Oh, wow
Um, I'm a little thirsty all of a sudden
I'm gonna go have some more tea
Okay
Why am I like this?
I just told him he's coming with me everywhere
Just you and me?
Seriously?
I'm so glad he can't see how red my face is
I look like a loser lobster
Hold up
Oh my god
This means I'm gonna be with him all summer break
I literally cannot
But I will
Holy crap
Huh?
Wow
She wasn't joking
He looks amazing
Whoa
Gojo
Are you okay?
What's on me?
Oh, gross
It's seaweed
It's slimy
And sticky
And all over
Gojo
It's not gonna eat you
You do this
It's just a plan
I just wanted to go a bit further
And then I slipped on this stuff
And fell in
You look like a trapped sticky rat
Oh, great
I can't go home like this
You'll try off by then?
Maybe
接着し Foster
With grateful
With unmuted
けし?
わたしきっと
恋してるの
運命のいたずら
その一言
つきゅぼきたの
Ah, this is what I'm waiting for
Now I'm going to be two together
A pure pure heart
The heart that is
I don't want to be two
I don't want to be too
To me, I'm trying to talk about
How do I mean to you?
So can I only take my own
These singing the same stage
Just as soon as I walk you,
Next time!